(Leonard:)So don't call her.
(Raj:)If I don't call her,
I won't hear the end of it.
- So call her.
- How can I call her? I can't talk to women.
(Leonard:)I'm done. Anybody else?
[GRUNTS]
- Give me the phone.
- Why?
Just give it to me. Sh.
- What are you doing?
- Don't worry, you'll thank me.
[IMITATING RAJESH]
Hello, Lalita? Raj Koothrappali.
[LAUGHING]
(Howard:)Yes, it is good to talk to you too.
So, what are you wearing?
(Howard:)Oh, not important.
(Howard:)So anyhow,
when would you like to meet?
(Howard:)Friday works for me.
I'll call you with a time and place.
(Howard:)In the meantime, keep it real, babe.
[NORMAL VOICE]
You may now thank me.
(Raj:)For what, making me sound
like a Simpsons character?